Greenbaum, Marcia Audio-Visual Materials 6091 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marcia Greenbaum Audio-Visual Materials
1990-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Greenbaum, Marcia
6091 AV
1.89 cubic feet
1.9 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
8233948
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 21, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6091: Marcia Greenbaum Papers
Greenbaum, Marcia L.
8233948
- ABCC Hearing - Boston Garden - Tape 1 (Box 1)
- ABCC Hearing - Boston Garden - Tape 2 (Box 2)
- ABCC Hearing - Boston Garden - Tape 3 (Box 3)
- Newton/Police - 9/6/1977 (Box 4)
- unknown (Box 5)
  Scope and Contents
  handwriting on tape is very hard to read, but, it is labeled
- Grievance in Hammond Construction - January 13, 1977 (Box 6)
- Newton/Police -- 10/3/1977 (Box 7)
- Fred Bradley (Box 8)
- Tape for Parent Case - Chandler Evans (Box 9)
- Roger Dean (Box 10)
- Newton/Police - 9/27/1977 (Box 11)
- Newton/Police - 9/27/1977 (Box 12)
- Union X3 - Piece of Steel Plate from a Flexographic I S machine - with polymer, 1 (Box 13)
- Union X2 - Piece of an Aluminum Plate from a 290 Letter flex Machine with Photopolymer Raised Type, 2 (Box 13)
- Ruff in Blades Baham - open reel audio tape, 3 (Box 13)
- South America: Route and Terminal Area Briefing -- 2/92 -- found in box 65 of 6091, and moved here, 1992; 4 (Box 13)
- Amy Gizzarelli Termination/State of R.I. (Box 14)
  This cassette was discovered in box 95, ff 8 of 6091, and moved to here
- Guy D. Bateman - 6/7/90, LEB ARPT Mngr. - 7/15/90, 1990 (Box 15)
  This cassette was discovered in box 45, ff 7 of 6091, and moved to here